Here, here.
This is Chenggong Pier.
Usually,
we locals
also like to come here and stroll around.
There's also a park behind here.
You guys can go down and walk around later
to experience
the slowness and openness of Nan'an.
By the way.
That boat on the river,
everyone calls it
Chenggong Chuanshuo.
It's a moving scenery on the Xixi River in Nan'an.
Ms. Xing,
have you ever taken the Chenggong boat?
No.
What a coincidence.
You can try to take it today.
No.
Let's go to the next spot.
Ms. Xing,
Feifei,
I think it's actually possible.
Xing Fei.
Have a seat.
Why do you always walk so fast?
You're too slow.
But you told me before
that your favorite city is Nan'an.
Although it's very slow here,
it's a place where you can feel happy.
Xing Fei.
Walk slower.
At least during the time before we reach the end.
Okay.
Let's just part on good terms.
Look, there's more here.
Can you catch it?
You all think I'm very mean, don't you?
A little.
Just a little?
The relationship between people
is inherently about treating each other equally.
You work hard out there
and bear most of the household expenses.
He takes care of you
and provides emotional value.
It's very fair.
That's only fair to me.
What do you mean?
Wang Jun studied design.
He is very talented.
But to support my startup,
he quit his job at the design institute.
He revolves around me every day
and hasn't picked up a paintbrush in a long time.
He loves you very much.
Would you give up your dream for love?
Is this really love?
What must be faced, must be faced.
Mr. Wang.
I'm fine.
She...
has always been like this.
No matter what happens,
she can always find the best solution.
She is very smart.
That's why I like her.
Then,
are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
After tomorrow's itinerary,
we will officially break up.
I don't want to use her family card before the end.
It's too pathetic.
What does this have to do with the family card?
Director Li warned me privately,
telling me not to use your toilet paper.
She said your toilet paper
costs ten yuan a piece.
No,
I've washed my hands of that a long time ago.
What nonsense is she talking about?
To her,
I'm just a complete jerk.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
I...
I'm fine.
Take it.
It's pretty cold outside.
Thank you.
No need.
It's free.
I don't need it even if it's free.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You and Zhang Yang...
Maybe we should just call it off.
Why so sudden?
It's not sudden.
I'm serious.
There are various reasons.
I'm not sure yet,
but it's pretty much decided.
No matter what,
I support you.
Tomorrow is the last day for the final order
before the new year.
Let's do our best.
The last day.
I heard you're still awake.
Is there a problem with your work?
I happen to be free today,
so I can do it with you.
No, thanks.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
It was my fault before.
I wasn't good enough.
I don't blame you at all,
or mean to be angry with you.
I just think
that our way of getting along
should go back to the way it was before.
It's better when everyone is
more comfortable.
Please don't overthink it.
It has nothing to do with you.
It really doesn't.
Well,
it's not late.
It's getting late.
Go to bed early.
By the way,
this ring.
My sister saw it last time,
and I only knew about it after she mentioned it.
It's not cheap, right?
It's not appropriate for me to keep it.
You keep it.
It's better if you keep it.
You know, people are funny.
We're already divorced.
Yet on such a cold day,
I waited in line for three hours
just to buy this for you.
Do I have too much time on my hands?
Yes.
How are things with Qianqian?
Why bring her up?
We weren't a match.
We broke up ages ago.
Qian Cheng.
How come you were so shrewd when you were with me,
but with someone else,
before the wedding even happened,
you got scammed out of all your money?
What? Who told you that?
Bad news travels fast.
Don't listen to their nonsense.
Besides,
people shouldn't always look back.
We have to look forward.
In the past...
In the past,
besides me,
your favorite thing was this walnut cookie.
Do you remember?
When we first got together,
no matter how cold it was
or how long the line was,
I always made sure you got to eat this.
It was fun back then, too.
When I was with you,
I didn't even feel cold.
Yes.
In the past.
The tag is still on.
I have so many clothes at home.
Just grab one and it's brand new.
Stop pretending.
All your money was scammed,
and you're here reminiscing about the past with me.
Let me tell you.
The boss of this walnut cake shop has changed.
You don't need to queue anymore,
and it doesn't taste like this anymore.
Li Yiying,
stop right there.
Let me ask you one last time,
do you need a driver?
What about a security guard?
You.
A man kicked out is like spilled water.
Great,
now I can't return the clothes.
The beans in this cafe
are all locally selected,
and their pour-over technique is very particular.
We Nan'an people often say,
a cup of coffee brings half a day of leisure.
Staying here
makes you feel like time slows down.
So,
you need to leave some blank space in life
to savor more flavors.
You can understand it that way.
So,
whether it's coffee or something else,
it needs proper extraction and time,
as well as...
Once this cup is finished,
the next one won't be the same.
If you drink again,
it's a new cup.
Right?
Then,
congratulations.
Thank you.
Between us,
there's no need for thanks.
The words we've said
and the time we've spent
will be like the aroma of coffee,
staying in our memories
and influencing each other's future lives.
I understand.
I know.
It's just that you're walking too fast,
and I can't keep up anymore.
Wang Jun.
Let's each go and become
a complete,
new cup of coffee.
You will also find
someone who appreciates your flavor.
And I
must also adapt to the concentration I chose.
Zhang Yang.
If,
I mean if,
this cafe changed its coffee beans,
would you still come?
Even if the beans changed,
the cafe wouldn't change.
But,
changing the beans changes the taste.
Just because the beans changed,
does the cafe have no chance?
Maybe.
It's just the person drinking the coffee who changed.
Sis.
A few days ago,
I received an offer from
a large travel agency in Beijing.
The salary and benefits they offered are quite good.
I thought about it.
The career prospects are definitely better there.
Leaving things here in Nan'an to you,
I can rest assured.
Is that why you lost interest in him?
I didn't lose interest.
I just feel...
Long-distance relationships rarely work out.
Rather than getting heartbroken later,
I might as well not start it.
Good thing it hasn't started yet.
Does he know?
I haven't told him.
It's a bit
hard for me to bring up.
Xinyue.
Do you not believe in love anymore?
Everyone's fate is different.
I can't be your reference.
Just because I was wrong before
doesn't mean I'll be wrong in the future.
But right now, you are right.
You must cherish it.
But sister,
do you really think I'm right?